World leaders, particularly America and China, are taking AI seriously.
Biden and Xi Jinping have already held talks about it.
The fact that these world powers are discussing AI is promising.
The UN Secretary General even mentioned that he's open to creating an international body for AI research.
This cooperation could create a strong foundation for global AI governance.
A recent study involving 2,700 AI researchers predicted job automation by 2100.
However, that doesn't align with the rapid advancements we're witnessing.
Job automation is likely to come much sooner than anticipated.
People like us are crucial to share this knowledge on platforms like YouTube.
Having an optimistic outlook on AI is rare but necessary.
Mustafa Suleyman was asked if AI could take over humanity.
He decisively shut down that idea, stating there is no likelihood of such an outcome.
This contradicts the common fear many have about AI.
His assurance is significant coming from someone behind major AI advancements.
It's encouraging to see industry leaders aligning with a positive view on AI's future.